Zephaniah Chekelea

Pursuing Business Analyst/Consultant-type role

Looking to further my skills and education to earn a role as a business analyst/consultant to leverage 5 years of proficiency in Salesforce from an admin/dev role. I last worked as the business lead for integrating conversational AI into our Customer Service voice, text and live chat channels. My passion lies with finding ways to digitally transform todays' processes with tomorrow's technology.



Zephaniahc@live.com



817-308-5127



Grapevine, TX



linkedin.com/in/zephaniahchekelea

SKILLS

SAP Hybris

Lean Six Sigma- Green Belt

Python

Conversational Al

Salesforce Administrator

Tableau

WordPress

Oracle Live SQL

AWS Cloud Practioner

SOL MGMT Studio

Public Speaking

Decision making

Agile Methodology

Jira Backlog

EDUCATION

B.S. in Information Technology and Systems

The University of Texas at Dallas

08/2015 - 05/2020

M.S. in Advanced Data Analytics

Toulouse Graduate School-University of North Texas

08/2022 - Present

WORK EXPERIENCE

Customer Technology Business Analyst- Service Cloud/NA SFDC Process Owner

Alcon Labs

07/2020 - 12/2022

Achievements/Tasks

- Delivered Salesforce Lightning Console to US Customer Service team with the addition of an agent console and a customer360 dashboard for service agents to provide more efficient service to customers
- Delivered 250+ enhancements since the year 2020 to improve the UI for customer care agents
- Built initiatives to automate daily processes for the US Customer Service team such as through webto-case functionality, simpler access to order history housed in SAP, email-to-case functionality and conversational AI
- Took a lead role in business improvement projects by compiling business needs with data housed in our Foresight data lake and working with major stakeholders to enhance customer service UX

Contact: Jennifer Roberts-Email: jennifer.roberts@alcon.com

Customer Service Intern

Alcon Labs

05/2019 - 07/2020

Fort Worth, TX

Achievements/Tasks

- Built and provided a scope for Salesforce Lightning implementation process for the entire US Customer Service team
- Analyzed current business needs within Salesforce Service Cloud by shadowing more than 20 end users and compiled/researched Lightning Experience features to utilize in the future for a better UX
- Constructed user-friendly page layouts for end users within a sandbox environment, trained them
 within their production environment and managed enhancement requests in an Agile environment
 using Jira system

Contact: Jim Ahlfinger - Email: jim.ahlfinger@alcon365.com

LANGUAGES

Telugu

Full Professional Proficiency

LANGUAGES

English

Native or Bilingual Proficiency

Hind

Professional Working Proficiency

Spanish

Limited Working Proficiency

INTERESTS

Traveling

Music

Sports

Cloud-based technology

Leader

Social work

WORK EXPERIENCE

Part-Time Web Designer/Content Manager/Sales Analyst Rejoice Christian Media LLC

06/2018 - 05/2019

Achievements/Tasks

- Promoted over 25 gospel albums by artists centrally located in India and Pakistan via uploading albums and handling key features in the Rejoice Christian Media website that included music sampling and mp3 downloads
- Analyzed monthly sales reports that came from the Rejoice Christian Media website through tuneCORE and gave market advice to musicians which resulted in a 15% growth in sales from June to July
- Updated web content with the latest blog posts, videos and mp3 files for new album releases

ORGANIZATIONS

Comet Tutors (10/2017 - 12/2017)

Worked with AVID students at JJ Pearce High School to help them with classes and adopt better practices for college prep

Salesforce Student Chapter, UT Dallas (08/2018 - 08/2019)

Completed trailheads with a focus in Lightning Experience implementation and designing a better Web UX

Alcon Young Professionals (05/2022 - Present)

Working as a mentee and mentor to several Summer interns

PERSONAL PROJECTS

Completed case studies as a part of Salesforce Developers course

- Created workflows that pertain to tasks as simple as requesting a vacation/medical leave
- Built a portal that allows users to access other users' data within the Salesforce system through shared permission sets and administrator delegated groups
- Used Apex programming to create web and email services